[{"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Who was the only African-American awarded an Oscar for an acting performance in one of the 100 American films on AFIs list?", "correct_answer": "Hattie McDaniel", "incorrect_answers": ["Sidney Poitier", "Cedric the Entertainer", "Morgan Freeman"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Which 1990 film does this strange sounding quote come from?\nIf things have gone wrong, Im talking to myself, and youve got a wet towel wrapped around your head.", "correct_answer": "Total Recall", "incorrect_answers": ["The Fifth Element", "The Hitch-Hikers Guide to the Galaxy", "Judge Dredd"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What boxer does Robert De Niro portray in the classic 80s movie Raging Bull?", "correct_answer": "Jake LaMotta", "incorrect_answers": ["Rocky Marciano", "Willy Pep", "Rocky Graziano"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Vanessa Hudgens, one of the stars in High School Musical, made her acting debut in the film Thirteen.", "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Can you name the movie from which this line is taken? What you have done is a felony for which you could be issued a fine or time in a state correctional facility.", "correct_answer": "The Cable Guy", "incorrect_answers": ["Cops", "How High", "Friday"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "About 50% of the weight of a well-fed sloth comprises of the food in its stomach.", "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Lassie and Benji are the same breed of dog.", "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "In the 2004 movie Dodgeball, the two sportscasters for ESPN 8 The Ocho covering the dodgeball championship were Pepper Brooks and who else?", "correct_answer": "Cotton McKnight", "incorrect_answers": ["Ty Webb", "Brick Tamland", "Wes Mantooth"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "People of what occupation wear the traditional Zucchetto cap?", "correct_answer": "Clergymen", "incorrect_answers": ["Samurai", "Baseball players", "Chefs"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "In the movie Saturday Night Fever, Toni Manero was the indisputable king at the disco, where he forgot about his dead-end job. What did Tony actually do for a living?", "correct_answer": "He worked in a paint store.", "incorrect_answers": ["He worked in a Pizza Parlor.", "He worked as a dance instructor.", "He was a stock boy at the local AP"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "White Goodman from the movie Dodgeball first met Kate Veatch in his office at Globo Gym. White tried to impress Kate by pretending to read this book when she walked in to meet him.", "correct_answer": "Websters dictionary", "incorrect_answers": ["Dantes Inferno", "The Sports Almanac", "Candide"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Two thirds of a sharks brain is dedicated to its sense of smell.", "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]}]